SUMAYA MARHOON AL HASNI

EXECUTIVE ADMINISTRATOR

SKILLSET

Empathy

Effective Communication
Teamwork
Leadership
Innovation
Advanced Administration & Secretarial
Reliability
Problem-solving
Determination

Adaptability Detail-oriented Bilingual: Arabic & English

EDUCATION

High School Diploma (Thanawiyyah) Dohat Al Adab Secondary School (Girls) 1998

Muscat || Oman

CONTACT

+968 9925 2343 sumayaalhasni0@gmail.com Muscat || Oman

PROFILE

With over two decades of experience in administrative and secretarial work, particularly with executive-level management, I am confident with my skillset to continue to bring success in the workplace. What your organization needs is what I have to offer, therefore, having me in your administration department will be one of your greatest hires as I will bring value and make a significant impact.

EXPERIENCE

EXECTUVE ADMIN OFFICER (OPERATION INVENTORY)

NATIONAL OIL WELL VARCO | MUSCAT | OCT 2011-MAR 2022

- Frequently update the bit movement and drilling tools daily in the inventory sheet and in TAT & JDE accordingly.
- Manage the Kronos daily for all staff annual leaves, sick leaves, and check-in and out timings.
- Conduct Annual Physical Inventory check.
- Manage outgoing shipments (prepare shipping documents according to the requirement, confirm the condition of the bit prior to shipping, make necessary TAT movements, and follow up till the bit is received at the designation).
- Manage repair facility, creating and issuing WO.
- Follow the upcoming Tenders.
- Arrange and follow up for the training will be held in Oman.
- Handle hotel booking arrangements for staff and visitors.
- Schedule appointments, interviews, visits and communications of the Management offices and arrange guest reception.

ASSISTANT MANAGER

BIN ZAID INTERNATIONAL INVESTMENTS | MUSCAT MAY 2000 - JAN 2011

- Began as an Executive Secretary managing all the admin work for the
 CFO
- Promoted to an Assisted Manager leading most of the administrative responsibilities of the company.

CHAIRMAN SECRETARY

AL TAUQI OMAN CO. | MUSCAT | JUL 1998 - MAR 2000

- Prepared correspondence for various ministries.
- Engaged in secretarial duties and handled all incoming and outgoing calls.
- Wrote letters and reports for the general office.

TRAINING

JDE TRAINING

DUBAI | UAE | AUG 2013 (VIA NATIONAL OIL WELL VARCO)

KRONOS CRP

DUBAI | UAE | SEPT 2012 (VIA NATIONAL OIL WELL VARCO)

LOGISTICS TEAMS - NOVDEL JDE & TAT

DUBAI | UAE | AUG 2012 (VIA NATIONAL OIL WELL VARCO)

MFG PRO

DUBAI | UAE | APR 2012 (VIA NATIONAL OIL WELL VARCO)